<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Interstate Drug and Alcohol Testing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Interstate Drug and ]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/blog-1</link><generator>RSS for Node</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 21:44:11 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.interstatemi.com/blog-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title><![CDATA[We Are Here For Your Drug Testing Needs]]></title><description><![CDATA[Interstate Drug &#38; Alcohol Testing is conveniently located in the central Upper Peninsula. We specialize in all your testing needs: Drug...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/we-are-here-for-your-drug-testing-needs</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5d768925329f6200170341e4</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 17:41:21 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_f214d73933104e108d91a9a4f5435a7b~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_821,h_645,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Interstate Drug &amp; Alcohol Testing is conveniently located in the central Upper Peninsula. We specialize in all your testing needs: Drug and Alcohol testing for DOT and non-DOT, regulated and non-regulated with certified technicians, Electronic CCF&apos;s, Form Fox, pre-employment, random, reasonable suspicion/cause, post accident, return to duty, follow up, breath alcohol testing, occupational health, hair testing, DNA testing, ETG urine alcohol testing, probation/court testing, breath test after ignition lockout, oral fluid testing. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>If you are searching for &quot;drug testing near me,&quot; make Interstate Drug &amp; Alcohol Testing your provider for your employee drug testing. Find us at Ludington Street and 11th Street in the Ludington Centre in downtown Escanaba. Call (906) 399-4574 to schedule an appointment that&apos;s convenient for you. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_f214d73933104e108d91a9a4f5435a7b~mv2.png/v1/fit/w_821,h_645,al_c,q_80/file.png"title="Interstate Drug & Alcohol Testing serves the Upper Peninsula of Michigan and northern Wisconsin."alt="Interstate Drug & Alcohol Testing serves the Upper Peninsula of Michigan and northern Wisconsin."></figure>
<p><br /></p>
<p><br /></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Don't Get The Runaround When Scheduling Your Drug Test]]></title><description><![CDATA[Nobody wants to get a drug test, but when you need one, you don't want to waste your time when setting it up and getting it collected....]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/2019/08/01/dont-get-the-runaround-when-scheduling-your-drug-test</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6007f65df6fed40017a57a7b</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2019 18:44:27 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_3556a16036b54fcfa0e34635102eba43~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_720,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Nobody wants to get a drug test, but when you need one, you don&apos;t want to waste your time when setting it up and getting it collected. You want to make one phone call and get on the calendar for a time that works for YOU - same day or next day appointments. And once you&apos;re in the door, you don&apos;t want to get forgotten in some waiting room somewhere. </p>
<p> </p>
<p>That&apos;s why you only want to schedule your drug and alcohol testing with Interstate Drug &amp; Alcohol Testing in Escanaba. </p>
<p> </p>
<p>You will get convenient, individualized attention from phone call to collection, dealing directly with the business owner, a certified Drug Test Collector and Breath Alcohol Technician, through the whole process. You can expect to spend around 10 minutes for your drug screen. Don&apos;t waste your valuable time trying to schedule anywhere else!</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Our location at the Ludington Centre in downtown Escanaba is quick in and out, with easy access and parking on Ludington Street or 11th Street.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>If great customer service without the runaround is what you&apos;re looking for, call Cindy for your testing at 906-399-4574</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_3556a16036b54fcfa0e34635102eba43~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_720,al_c,q_80/file.png"alt="Don't get frustrated - Call Interstate Drug & Alcohol Testing"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Affordable Drug Testing in Michigan's Upper Peninsula]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tired of paying too much for employee drug testing? Here's one way to lower your employee drug and alcohol testing costs: Do all your...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/affordable-drug-testing-in-michigan-s-upper-peninsula</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5d14f7c8218ccb0016b5579c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 17:38:42 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_7b3488bf6c45483fbf33a68c7052d19b~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_900,h_598,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Tired of paying too much for employee drug testing? Here&apos;s one way to lower your employee drug and alcohol testing costs:</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Do all your employee testing at Interstate Drug &amp; Alcohol Testing in centrally located Escanaba, Michigan.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Price it out. We offer the best rates. Plus we are centrally located in the U.P. of Michigan in downtown Escanaba in Delta County. We are convenient to anywhere in the UP with our easy-to-reach central UP location. Get to us quick from Marquette, Schoolcraft, Alger, Menominee, Dickinson, Iron, Baraga, Houghton, Keweenaw, Ontonagon, Gogebic, Luce, Mackinac, and Chippewa Counties. We are in the middle of them all!</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>We work with SAMHSA and HHS certified labs. We work with all industries and regulatory agencies: trucker&apos;s FMCSA, aviation FAA, railroad FRA, public transportation FTA, pipline PHMSA, maritime USCG.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Our focus is customer service and speedy test results. Call today to schedule an appointment 906-399-4574.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_7b3488bf6c45483fbf33a68c7052d19b~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_900,h_598,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p><br /></p>
<p><br /></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We Can Drug Test for You]]></title><description><![CDATA[Did you know that we perform drug testing for manufacturing facilities, restaurants and food service, healthcare field, and personal or...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/2019/06/06/we-can-drug-test-for-you</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6007f65df6fed40017a57a77</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 17:45:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_6815dd1a1dd9493789833eebb2d05d0e~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_853,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Did you know that we perform drug testing for manufacturing facilities, restaurants and food service, healthcare field, and personal or attorney requested? Call today to schedule an appointment. Fast test result turnaround. Call today 906-399-4574.</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_6815dd1a1dd9493789833eebb2d05d0e~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_853,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[3  Reasons to Use Oral Fluid Drug Testing for Your Employees]]></title><description><![CDATA[Every drug and donor is different, but oral fluid testing is considered one of the most reliable specimen types for detecting recent drug...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/3-reasons-to-use-oral-fluid-drug-testing-for-your-employees</link><guid isPermaLink="false">5ccb0bce21a50b01f2131a74</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 15:43:55 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_c92e49f284b647f883efa6cea7706604~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_853,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Every drug and donor is different, but oral fluid testing is considered one of the most reliable specimen types for detecting recent drug use. Here are three compelling reasons to request a Oral Fluid Drug Screen for your employees:</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>1. Accurate, immediate drug detection system.</strong> Oral fluid testing is excellent at detecting recent drug use. It can identify drugs in the system immediately, to determine drugs in the system at the time of the drug test collection. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>2. Self-collected in presence of a monitor. </strong> Donors collect their own oral fluid sample in the presence of a monitor, making it difficult for a donor to cheat or adulterate the sample. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>3. Quick, accurate results.</strong> Collection is quick and easy, with negative lab results available the next business day and positive lab results available within 72 hours. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Conveniently located at 1100 Ludington Street, Suite 205  in Escanaba, MI. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Contact Interstate Drug &amp; Alcohol Testing to schedule a screening today 906-399-4574. </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_c92e49f284b647f883efa6cea7706604~mv2.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_853,al_c,q_80/file.png"title="Oral fluid drug testing available at Interstate Drug & Alcohol Testing in Escanaba, MI."alt="Oral fluid drug testing available at Interstate Drug & Alcohol Testing in Escanaba, MI."></figure>
<p><br /></p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Top Reasons to Have a Drug Testing Program]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you're an employer and you've ever had problems with drunk or high employees, you're probably considering putting a drug testing...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/2018/11/13/top-reasons-to-have-a-drug-testing-program</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6007f65df6fed40017a57a7d</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 19:01:23 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_13a1cca89d40436eadff96a946464630~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_640,h_423,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you&apos;re an employer and you&apos;ve ever had problems with drunk or high employees, you&apos;re probably considering putting a drug testing program in place.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Here are the top reasons to get started now:</p>
<p> </p>
<p>1. Prevent hiring candidates who use drugs - pre-employment drug testing standards</p>
<p>2. Provide a safe workplace - cut back on accidents and crime</p>
<p>3. Increase employee productivity - reduce absences, employee turnover</p>
<p>4. Improve company morale - creates a positive workplace</p>
<p>5. Protect company image - boost customer confidence in quality and service</p>
<p>6. Reduce employer liability - protect employees, customers and the public and manage healthcare and insurance costs</p>
<p>7. Deter drug and alcohol use - help identify employees who need help with rehabilitation for substance use</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Interstate Drug &amp; Alcohol Testing can help you implement the drug &amp; alcohol testing policy that&apos;s right for your company. And we&apos;ll make it easy for you to get your employees tested at our downtown Escanaba clinic, or on-site at your location. Call 906-399-4574 or email cindy@interstatemi.com to get started. </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_ba70436810bb49bc867f963a515e6dc6~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_640,h_426,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_13a1cca89d40436eadff96a946464630~mv2.jpeg/v1/fit/w_640,h_423,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We serve the Upper Peninsula of Michigan]]></title><description><![CDATA[We are a drug and alcohol testing and collection site for all communities in Michigan's Upper Peninsula. We are centrally located in...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/2018/09/25/we-serve-the-upper-peninsula-of-michigan</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6007f65df6fed40017a57a7c</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 18:36:29 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b128108c51614e349e55ac30253ba194.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>We are a drug and alcohol testing and collection site for all communities in Michigan&apos;s Upper Peninsula.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>We are centrally located in Escanaba, within an hour radius of the following communities:</p>
<p>Gladstone, Rapid River, Bark River, Powers, Cornell, Menominee, Nahma, Garden, Isabella, Manistique, Trenary, Iron Mountain, Harris, Norway, Kingsford, Carney, Stephenson, Wallace, Hermansville, Schaffer, Gwinn.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>We are within a two hour drive of the following communities:  Marquette, Munising, Ishpeming, Negaunee, Crystal Falls, Baraga, L&apos;Anse, Marinette, Niagara, Iron River, Gulliver, Engadine, Newberry, Little Lake.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Within a three hour drive for the rest of the U.P.:  Sault Ste. Marie, St. Ignace, Brimley, Kinross, Rudyard, Naubinway, Ironwood, Houghton, Hancock, Ontonagon, Bessemer, Calumet, Copper Harbor, Florence, Pembine, Watersmeet, Wakefield.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>We are also a collection site for the following labs:  Quest, eScreen, Alere, Abbott, LabCorp, CRL, Medtox,</p>
<p> </p>
<p>To schedule your collection, call 906-399-4574.</p>
<p> </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/b128108c51614e349e55ac30253ba194.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pre-employment Drug Testing]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you are looking to set up pre-employment drug screening for your company, we can help you with that. 1st- Call Interstate Drug and...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/2018/08/28/pre-employment-drug-testing</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6007f65df6fed40017a57a79</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 18:58:37 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/42a76e155ac242cf93979ad39e5db58e.png/v1/fit/w_646,h_433,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you are looking to set up pre-employment drug screening for your company, we can help you with that. </p>
<p> </p>
<p>1st- Call Interstate Drug and Alcohol Testing 906-399-4574</p>
<p> </p>
<p>2nd- We will discuss your drug testing needs</p>
<p> </p>
<p>3rd- Customized testing program will be developed. We make it easy for you to send potential employees in for pre-employment drug testing.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>4th- We will send results, and now you are ready to hire the best candidate for your company!</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/42a76e155ac242cf93979ad39e5db58e.png/v1/fit/w_646,h_433,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Recovering your vehicle after breath alcohol device lockout]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you have been court ordered to have a breath alcohol device on your vehicle to keep your license or you have a work vehicle that...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/2018/07/26/recovering-your-vehicle-after-breath-alcohol-device-lockout</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6007f65df6fed40017a57a7a</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jul 2018 18:02:04 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/e31432360f4e493ba33016f413d775b1.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you have been court ordered to have a breath alcohol device on your vehicle to keep your license or you have a work vehicle that requires breath alcohol ignition testing prior to driving, and you&apos;ve been locked out, we can help.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Your IID or BAIID will lock your vehicle if your blood alcohol level exceeds the prescribed limit typically .025.  When this happens, you will have to be tested with an EtG (Ethyl glucuronide) urine test to prove that you are alcohol free.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>When you pass this test, the requesting party will then be able to remove the lockout on your ignition. </p>
<p> </p>
<p>Contact us for your EtG test and we can help you get back on the road!</p>
<p>906-399-4574</p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/e31432360f4e493ba33016f413d775b1.jpg/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Interstate Drug and Alcohol Testing Opens in Escanaba, Mi]]></title><description><![CDATA[Interstate Drug and Alcohol Testing has opened at 1100 Ludington Street in the Ludington Centre. The company specializes in non-DOT and...]]></description><link>https://www.interstatemi.com/post/2018/06/27/interstate-drug-and-alcohol-testing-opens-in-escanaba-mi</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6007f65df6fed40017a57a78</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 20:02:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_24b65d5a1f9f4e15988b4e0f6ee5419d~mv2_d_2113_2192_s_2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><dc:creator>Cindy@Interstate</dc:creator><content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Interstate Drug and Alcohol Testing has opened at 1100 Ludington Street in the Ludington Centre.</p>
<p>The company specializes in non-DOT and DOT drug testing and breath alcohol testing, </p>
<p>Owner Cindy Wallin invites you to make Interstate Drug and Alcohol Testing your main provider</p>
<p>for your drug and alcohol testing needs.</p>
<p>Contact Cindy at 906-399-4574</p>
<figure><img src="https://static.wixstatic.com/media/73ed3e_24b65d5a1f9f4e15988b4e0f6ee5419d~mv2_d_2113_2192_s_2.png/v1/fit/w_1000,h_1000,al_c,q_80/file.png"></figure>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>